industrialinterface.com 2009-11-03

# Privacy Policy | Industrial Interface, Inc.

## "Privacy Policy"

### Industrial Interface is owned and operated by:

Industrial Interface, Inc.   
321 10th Avenue, Suite 1501   
San Diego, CA 92101 

We can be reached via e-mail at [info@industrialinterface.com](mailto:info@industrialinterface.com)  
or you can reach us by telephone at 1.858.633.8158.

### Industrial Interface Privacy Policy

Industrial Interface maintains the following privacy policy to insure that our users remain confident that Industrial Interface has the sole intention of improving the industrial research, design, and manufacturing landscape. 

  1. This privacy policy is effective as of Jan 1, 2009. 
  2. Except as set forth in this privacy policy, your personal information will not be disclosed to any third parties. 
  3. Industrial Interface may collect and store information about pages within our site that you visit, as well as other information regarding referring sites. All other information that we store is considered part of your personal profile. Information from your personal profile is owned by Industrial Interface, but is subject to applicable California State privacy laws. 
  4. Your personal information may be shared with third parties to enhance your user experience. This includes, but is not limited to, formal agreements of partnership, information required to access third party application-programming interfaces (APIs), and other services. 
  5. To review, modify, or erase your personal information maintained by Industrial Interface you must submit a request via email to: info@industrialinterface.com. 
  6. Industrial Interface occasionally generates cookies. These are used to enhance your user experience. Data generated from these cookies may be used in accordance with governing privacy regulations of both the United States Federal Government as well as the State of California. 
  7. Information from your profile, or other information you have presented to Industrial Interface, may be used to generate private and public reports regarding, but not limited to, usage of Industrial Interface. 
  8. Industrial Interface will not sell your personal information to any third parties without first obtaining your permission. 
  9. Industrial Interface may transfer or share your information with corporate entities that purchase, merge with, or invest in Industrial Interface, or with other companies as Industrial Interface sees fit. 
  10. Notifications of changes to this privacy policy will be posted here prior to the changes taking affect.
